<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.rodinp.handbook.feature"
      label="Rodin Handbook v.2.5"
      version="2.5.0.201606291411"
      provider-name="Formal Mind GmbH">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      This handbook provides documentation for users of the Rodin toolset, which allows working with Event-B models. 

Event-B is a formal method for system-level modelling and analysis. Key features of Event-B are the use of set theory as a modelling notation, the use of refinement to represent systems at different abstraction levels and the use of mathematical proof to verify consistency between refinement levels.

The Rodin Platform is an Eclipse-based IDE for Event-B that provides effective support for refinement and mathematical proof. The
platform is open source, contributes to the Eclipse framework and is further extensible with plugins.

This handbook covers the use of the core platform. Documentation for developers and regarding extensions can be found in the Rodin
wiki. 

What you see here is a working draft of the documentation. We
are grateful for any feedback that you may have.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      (c) 2011 by Formal Mind GmbH and Others
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      This work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution Licens (CC BY).  The full license is found at

http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="Formal Mind" url="http://formalmind.com"/>
      <discovery label="Rodin Sourceforge" url="http://sourceforge.net/projects/rodin-b-sharp/"/>
      <discovery label="Rodin Handbook" url="http://handbook.event-b.org"/>
      <discovery label="Event-B" url="http://www.event-b.org"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="org.rodinp.handbook"
         download-size="8993"
         install-size="10679"
         version="2.5.0.201606291411"/>

</feature>
